631-482-6698 | rajdotdeliwala@gmail.com | rajdeliwala.github.io | github.com/RajDeliwala | linkedin.com/in/raj-deliwala

About Me

An enthusiastic and robust individual with 3.5+ years' experience and knowledge of industry seeking a new role. Focused on software engineering, system administration, data analysis, requirement gathering, creation of functional requirements, process flow analysis and design, functional and regression testing, database architectures, and content management analysis. Looking to expand a company's existing domain and software delivery platforms.

Programming Python - C/C++ - C# - Java - JavaScript - ASP .NET MVC 5.0

Technical Tools GitHub - Visual Studios - Linux/Unix OS - Android Studios - Eclipse - MobaXterm

Web/Databases HTML 5 - CSS 3 - Bootstrap - SQL - MySQL - Entity Framework - SQLite - SQL Server - VMware

Experience _____

AppleHardware / Software Test Engineer – MSQ

Austin, TX

Aug. 2021 – Present

Developed from the ground up a newly 2,000 SQFT lab in Austin, TX. Built a rack-based test environment for Mac related projects. Worked directly with California based MSQ (Mac System Quality) team to efficiently test large pools of Mac related projects, analyzing data to run further experiments and ensuring adherence to Apples high product standards .

- · Built lab testing environment from the ground up to support high level test loads and experiments
- Executing Factory and Stability based tests to ensure proper conditions per new OS build.
- Tested system state transitions, working with sleep wakes, cold bu, warm restart.
- Managed hundreds of Macs portable or desktop, MacBook Pro, AIR, and it is supporting infrastructure
- Daily triaging, kicking off or debugging previous test runs to ensure maximum system efficiency
- · Able to provide daily, timely, and meaningful results driven by tight product release schedule
- Clearly, concisely, and accurately report project status and results for hundreds of Mac units.
- Experience in managing a rack of systems running a variety of tests and engineering experiments

Flextronics Austin, TX

Software Test Engineer – Services

Jan. 2021 – Aug,2021

Flex works directly with CISCO to test a variety of products. Worked with CISCO servers running temperature, voltage, and network specific variations to comply with certain settings. Worked within the Services team to create, edit and run automation test scripts for migration onto a new cloud-based testing tool called APOLLO.

- Developed and used computer software and hardware to conduct tests on server units and systems.
- Resolved script issues by performing analysis of root causes, developing and coordination corrective action measures and monitoring improvements.
- Analyzed and interpreted test data to prepare technical reports for software engineering and management personnel.
- Communicated with engineering and technical personnel to resolve testing problems such as product or system malfunctions, incomplete test data, data interpretation or script issues.
- Determined conditions under which tests are run in isolated chambers and sequences/phases of test operations.
- Experienced filtering through legacy code on Autotest to re-write test scripts for cloud-based testing tool, Apollo. PYTHON PYCHARM AUTOTEST- APOLLO REDHAT BIT BUCKET LINUX/UNIX OS C/C++

Zebra Technologies

Software Test Engineer - DCS

Holtsville, NY

Nov. 2018 - Mar.2020

Zebra produces marking, tracking, and computing printing solutions to major clients such as Walmart and Costco. Products such as thermal barcode labels, hand-held scanners, RFID smart label printers and barcode optical scanners. Worked in the TnV (Testing and Validation) team under the DCS (Data Capture Solutions).

- · Experienced in developing and executing manual and automated tests in Python using Pytest.
- Wrote and edited automation scripts in python on a raspberry pi for newly assigned test builds.
- Designing and creating testing environments for hardware testing and debugging.
- Preformed functional and regression testing to promote quality assurance of products.
- Worked within the Software Testing Life Cycle to elevate and ensure key product features.
- Worked within agile sprints using black box testing methods to ensure efficient testing.
 PYTHON PYTEST JIRA CLEAR CASE EXCEL POLARIAN RASPBERRY PI

Education & Certifications

Farmingdale State College

ASP NET MVC Web Development

Farmingdale, NY Sept. 2014 – Dec. 2017

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE COMPUTER PROGRAMMING & INFORMATION SYSTEMS